waspbarcode.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy for Wasp Barcode

Wasp Barcode Technologies respects the privacy of visitors to its web site.  We place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors. Therefore, we have developed and share with you the following privacy policy. 

### **Personal Information**

We work to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards. When you register with Wasp, we will ask you for certain personal information.  The information may be combined with other information we have collected from you.  We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interaction on the Wasp site so we can constantly improve the experience you have.

### **Uses of Information**

When we ask you for information, we will tell you – or it will be clear – what we need to know to fulfill your request and how the information you provide to us will be used. For example, if you request a product demo for download, we will ask you for your name and contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address. Wasp may follow up with you after you have downloaded information. 

In addition to responding to your request, if you agree, we may use your contact information to send you information about Wasp products or services that might interest you or invite you to participate in a product or service-related survey.

Further, if you agree, Wasp may provide your information to an authorized business partner of Wasp Barcode Technologies for follow up. In this situation, the business partner is providing further assistance for product information and sales fulfillment based on your interest in a Wasp solution. 

We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone 

### Your choice and control

We may use your contact information to keep you informed of Wasp news & events, to tell you about new upgrades, or alert you to other Wasp products we think might interest you. However, if you don't want us to contact you, you can opt-out of future information releases.

### You can contact us

**

If you have privacy-related questions that are not addressed here or wish to contact Wasp about privacy-related issues, please contact us by writing to us at: Wasp Privacy, Wasp Barcode Technologies, 1400 10th Street, Plano, TX 75074.

**
